sharenet.co.za 2019-03-13

# SHARENET - Your Key To Investing

Sharenet is committed to respecting your privacy. Because we store certain types of information , we feel you should fully understand the terms and conditions surrounding the capture and use of this information. This privacy statement discloses what information we store and how we use it. Questions regarding this statement should be directed to: [support@sharenet.co.za](mailto:support@sharenet.co.za)

This policy complies with Section 51 of the Electronic Communications and Transactions Act, 2002.

**Capture and Use of Information**

Sharenet (Pty) Ltd is the sole owner of the information collected from visitors to our site. We will not sell, share, rent or disclose this information to other parties in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. 

In some instances, we may pass information to third parties involved in the relevant Sharenet Service (such as stock brokers who you specifically sign up with). You will generally know if such a transfer of your information happens. In order to comply with any valid legal process such as a search warrant, subpoena, statute, or court order, we may however be compelled to release specific personal information, but will afford you the opportunity to contest such requests as far as possible.

Material you post on interactive forums or chatrooms in Sharenet services will be available to others using the Service.

**Further information/marketing**

If you agree Sharenet may contact you about those of its services which may interest you by email and (in certain limited circumstances) by telephone. You have a right to ask us at any time not to contact you by way of direct marketing.

**Cookies**

"Cookies" are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. Generally, cookies work by assigning to your computer a unique number that has no meaning outside of our system. Our cookies do not contain any personally identifying information. We use them to provide website statistics regarding the number of unique visitors to our site and for counting impressions on our pages. Cookies are also used to store your preferences. (eg: customise the columns displayed on your portfolio). Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can change your browser to prevent that, although this may break certain other features of out site.

**IP Addresses**

Sharenet uses IP addresses to analyze trends, track visitor's movements, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. Based on the aggregated information gained from cookies and IP addresses, statistical reports are generated for use by Sharenet management and to aid in selling advertising in our free areas. Aggregate information will never identify you, it only defines site visitors in general terms.

**Security**

Sharenet takes every precaution to protect our users' information. We use multiple levels of security starting with SSL on your browser and ending with a trusted database and operating system.

See our Security Notice. 

**Notification of Changes**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our Homepage so our users are always aware of what information we collect and how we use it.
